this is great of course i would always invite you to the party you and meanie are always invited
and ugo is always invited as well oh thanks i really appreciate that claudia i thought
that i would take a moment to let your audience know a little about ifco and give you a little
break since you've been you know yapping it up all day listen i've been talking so much i really do
need to drink water so i'm going to drink water and i'm going to let you talk about ifco for a
little bit how about that will do so the interreligious foundation for community organization
or ifco was founded in 1967 by progressive church leaders and activists and it's the first national
foundation led by people of color and for over 40 years ifco has supported community organizations
and public policy groups fighting for justice and self-determination by providing technical
assistance training organizers administering grants and using its global network of grassroots
organizers quirky and other professionals to advance the struggles for justice and self-determination
of the oppressed ifco is sending 30 tons of aid to cuba the trump administration has escalated the u.s
blockade on cuba making daily life so much harder for our neighbors and ifco is working on a shipment
container headed for cuba in the summer of 2026 so help us send critical aid to our siblings living
under a deadly u.s imposed blockade that is making everyday life harder and harder ifco is working on
i'm doing my best though and i'm kind of nervous i'm not nervous you're doing great thanks anyway we're
raising money towards assembling and shipping hundreds of boxes of medical equipment essential medicines and
vitamins surgical supplies contraceptives feminine feminine hygiene products uh non-perishable pantry
items bicycles school supplies i love school that was great thank you so much i think you did a great
job describing ifco and you did a great job describing why we are here today um i want to get the count of
how much we have raised but i want to see that yeah can we get a count of how much we've raised today